PRAPAS KHONG-ATTAGARN

Bangna District, Bangkok, 10260prapas.k13@hotmail.com

(+66)8-606-97918

in prapas-k

Location: open, no restriction





GOAL

To be Software developer or AI Engineer

INTRODUCE

Let's start with graphic designer for 7 years with extensive experiences in print design poster name card and banner.

I am ambitious and curious new things, not to good talker but good to listener, Expect to working in tech area with very talented team. I have a passionate to Artificial intelligence to create innovative or combination of tech and design together for better results.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Responsibilities

Present Enhancing skills in web development React(typescript), Node.js

DSA through online courses and self-study.

• Graphic Designer @ OSCAR GRAPHIC Contact for 3 months. (DEC 2019 - FEB 2020)

 Design, edit and develop an artwork offline media like banner, poster, sticker label and namecard.

- Produce some work pieces as well.

Achievements - Many clients trust and let me to be partner on new projects again.

• Coordinator Designer @ DKSH (Thailand) Probation for 5 months. (NOV 2018 - APR 2019)

Responsibilities - Design events area to set position of furniture.

- Control the installation before the event day.

- Supports senior designer.

Achievements - Design events area ranging from 25 sqm. up to shop in the mall

to support at least 50 customers.

Graphic Designer @ SIAM PARAGON DEVELOPMENT Officer for 6 years.

(JUN 2012 - APR 2018)

Responsibilities - Design, edit and develop an artwork offline media like banner,

poster and photo backdrop.

- Production control check pantone colour before produce.

Achievements - To be a part of team that create big project in the mall make a good experience for customers via graphic design and print media.

- Reduce the cost of hiring an agency.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES



FINAL PROJECT IN BOOT CAMP

 Build web application with MERN STACK CRUD

"Goal to fit" - activity traking

- Takes 2 - 3 months to do

OTHERS ACHIEVEMENTS

Web Application 2023

Matrix calculator
html, scss, javascript, python

- Maze game

html, scss, javascript

- Draw pixels art

html, scss, javascript

 Algo arithmetic puzzle game html, scss, javascript

CERTIFICATES

Certification of junior Software Developer Program (2022)
a 12-week-full-time bootcamp: Generation Thailand

Certification of Create a Front-End App with React Skill Path (2022)
Online course : Codecademy

Certification of Node.js Course (2022)

Online course : Codecademy



Check my projects https://barrimos.github.io

COURSES

• Junior software developer : MERN stack technology @ Generation Thailand. 1/2022 - 4/2022 : 3 months

- Learned how to build web applications from React as front-end, Node.js as back end, and MongoDB as a Database.

- Learned essential skills for switching careers, such as growth mindset, communication, agile, and teamwork.

- Learned bihavioral skills to be a good worker.

Web develop : HTML CSS PHP SQL @ Tutortong.
Basic 3d model sculpting : Zbrush @ Z-LA digital arts.
Basic 3ds Max model and lighting : 3ds Max @ Utahtd 3d tutor.
5/2019 - 7/2019 : 3 months
5/2018 - 7/2018 : 3 months

EDUCATION